One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
Fourth Level - The Sunflower Field
Well? What are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do?
The ground is rippling like a flag.
How pathetic! Just grovel in the dust, Toy Soldier!
Cabbage and Lomeo
I get it! It all makes sense now.
The toy soldier who was crying and screaming so disgracefully back then...
That was you!
Scarlett!
You're the late Scarlett's husband and Rebecca's father.
This is great!
Looks like you and I are bound by karma, eh Kyros?
That's right!
That's why I came here!
Oh, oops... That was a good move!
But it's a steel cape. Watch out!
Vipera Glaive!
Snake Sword
Father!
Father, I'll fight, too!
Yeah! Fight, Rebecca! I'll kill you!
I wanna watch Kyros lose both his wife and daughter!
It's okay, Rebecca!
Let me protect you, as well as atone for Scarlett's death!
Let me compensate for teaching you how to fight!
I've been living with regret and shame for it until today!
Now that I've become human once more,
I will never let my daughter swing a sword again!
Th-This is terrible...
Royal Palace Grounds - Second Level
Lao G-sama was taken out!
That's some power.
I've heard that name before.
The Happou Navy from the Flower Kingdom.
I'll keep it in mind.
Anyone can become our enemy at any time.
Gramps! Hey, Gramps!
Don't die, Gramps!
Then I'll reserve two ceremonial halls, honey!
Ceremonial halls?! Honey?!
For the wedding and...
the funeral.
Don't write us off!
Royal Palace Grounds - Third Level
Why are you crawling and slinking around?
Now, fight me, Gladius!
Don't push your luck.
What the...
No! Gladius-sama, you can't!
The ground is inflating!?
You know what'll happen, don't you?
You were preparing for this?
Watch out!
Run!
Hey, Bartolomeo! Everything's gonna blow!
Let me inside your barrier!
No way!
What?!
If I open it, Robin-senpai and I will be in danger, and our enemies will come inside as well!
No, open it! I'm on your side!
Gladius-sama! We'll be caught up in it, too...
It'll be fine. You guys are elite, right?
Open up!
Pop Rock...
Festival!
Goodbye, Cavendish.
If I'd been outside right now, I'd be a dead man.
You ingrate!
Why'd you wait so long to let me in?!
I thought I was gonna die!
What's wrong with you?!
That's no way to talk to the guy who just saved your life!
I was covering you before that! Now we're even!
I've had enough! I'm going to attack them!
Let me out!
What?!
I just let you in, and now you want out?!
Since you came in, why don't you stay for a while, you selfish fool?!
Is this an inn?!
Offense must come after defense!
That's how it should be!
I won't let you in next time!
Let me in again when I'm in danger!
You're so unreasonable!
I'll get you for this later!
Oh yeah, Robin-senpai!
Oh, great! She's alright!
I'll be there, Rebecca! Stay safe!
Nico Robin, you cumbersome woman!
I won't let you get in the way of the top commanders anymore!
Catapult Pop!
Bari-ability: Racket!
He's still alive?!
Advance! Robin-senpai!
Rooster-kun!
Thank you!
S-She made an eye gesture, a.k.a. a wink!
I'm so grateful!
Did it mean, "Good job, Rooster-kun! You can become my slave if you want"?!
No no, you're being too presumptuous, Bartolomeo! You're asking for too much!
But!
I'm getting real fired up!
Cavendish, you were in the barrier, too?!
Too bad, Gladius!
Blade of Beauty: Blue...
Bracchium...
Gladius-sama!
Bartolomeo!
Barrier Bulls!
The barrier is charging at us!
Robin-senpai! To a man, your eye gesture is worth risking his life!
Stop, Bartolomeo! Can't you see I'm here?!
Sorry, Cabbage! But there's a reason I can't stop!
And that is?!
I'm... so fired up!
I don't care!
What are you talking about, you fool?!
Stop now!
No can do!
Dellinger!
Haven't you cleaned up the second level yet?!
Gladius! What are you doing?
I'll be finished here soon!
Come and help on the third level!
Nico Robin is trying to make her way up!
My hands are full with these two idiots!
Roger! Sounds like fun!
Didn't I tell you...
to pay attention?!
Boy, you're so persistent, you Longhand!
I did think those protrusions on your shoulders were weird.
You got a hole in your damn stomach!
So why don't you drop dead already, Martial Arts Champion?
I can't do that!
You gotta have a sense of duty and obligation in a man's world!
I must fight for the sake of those who have already fallen!
That's so not you.
If you played dead or something, I would've spared your life.
How will staying on your feet help?!
Maybe I can buy some time.
We've gotta keep you guys from getting in Straw Hat's way...
so that he can defeat Doflamingo!
We'll do it together!
There's no such thing as victory attained by one person alone, kid!
So you guys are trying to attain victory
by sacrificing your lives.
That's how vermin act!
The strong don't heed obligations!
I'm no ordinary human, either.
Don't underestimate my Fighting Fish lineage!
3rd step
Gladius! I'm here!
Where are you?
Gladius!
Dellinger, stay on the lower level!
It's dangerous here!
We have one troublesome enemy!
That doesn't sound like you!
Gladius, nobody can oppose us when we fight together-
Dellinger!
Damn! Dellinger...
What the...
What just happened?!
That brat with horns and all the other enemy soldiers...
He took 'em all down.
There's this kinda scary guy on the other side of the barrier!
Wh-Who's that?
He looks like Cabbage, but his face is totally different.
This is exactly the same thing that happened in the Block D match at the Colosseum.
Oh my, everyone's gone down!
That was this guy's doing?
Those clothes are undoubtedly Cavendish's.
But the face looks undoubtedly like somebody else-dish.
So what kinda-vendish is he?
T-That scared me!
He was so fast, I couldn't see him!
Well, no matter how fast you can move, it's useless against my ability!
What the hell're you thinking?!
What's happened to you?!
If you take this joke too far...
Hey! Who did you just glance at?!
Don't do anything stupid! Hey! Hey!
Don't!
Don't go after Robin-senpai!
Your speed is useless against me.
Your face has become quite ugly.
Cabbage-kun, did you want something from me?
I'm worried about Rebecca, so I must hurry to the top.
Wow! Cool! She stopped him!
Dobin-sedbai!
I knew it was too audacious of a weakling like me to try to protect you!
Wait, Hakuba!
I didn't give you permission to come out!
I'm sorry, Nico Robin.
I almost cut you.
So that was this "Hakuba" I've heard about.
Your other personality...
That's right...
He's bad news.
He kills indiscrimi-
Your hands and feet...
I'll chop them and what's left of you into bits, Nico Robin!
I'll slice up everything!
Stay away, Hakuba! I won't let you take control!
Shut up! Stay asleep, Cavendish!
You don't even know what I'm fighting for!
I'll take care of this!
I'll just rip everything to shreds!
There's no point if I don't do it!
Don't care! I'll show them a bloodbath!
It's like two people having a conversation! Does he have a split personality?!
I will!
No, me!
I'll do it!
No, I will!
I will!
Me, me, me!
I will, I will, I will !
Me!
I will!
I will! Me!
He's gone half-and-half!
Shut up, Hakuba!
I'm the only Cavendish!
You were half-and-half just a second ago!
Okay, it's alright now, Nico Robin.
Why don't you let go of me?
You expect me to trust you after seeing that?
Huh?
Let's just end this now.
I'll blow you up along with the wall!
This'll do far worse than just throw you into the air.
You're not getting away in one piece!
That bastard!
He'll rupture us along with the wall!
We need to get down right now, Nico Robin!
No! Something could happen to Rebecca while I'm doing that...
Leave this to me!
I won't let him harm Robin-senpai!
Good judgment.
Yes, if you take me down, you can stop the wall from rupturing.
Punk Hair!
What's this? It went numb.
Those hairs are poison needles.
What?!
Bartolomeo!
I have the power of the Rupture Fruit.
In other words, I'm a rupture man from head to toe.
If you do something to me, my body will explode...
and thousands more of the poison needles that just caught you...
will pierce through those two up there!
But if you don't take me down, you can't stop the wall from rupturing.
What are you gonna do?
My body's explosion will be so powerful that you can't survive, of course.
Then Robin-senpai will suffer no matter what I do!
You're a fast learner, Bartolomeo.
Think, Bartolomeo!
What's the most important thing for me to keep safe here?
That's obviously...
Robin-senpai's body.
To stop the wall from rupturing,
I've gotta take that hedgehog down.
But then, all those poison needles will fly straight toward Robin-senpai!
What should I do? Think!
Think harder, Bartolomeo!
Oh yeah!
There's a completely expendable guy up there with Robin-senpai!
Hey, Cabbage! I'll bring down the hedgehog here, so...
you protect Robin-senpai from the poison needles by using your whole body as a shield!
Hey...
Hey, Cabbage!
Shut up, rooster!
The evil one came out again!
Just when I need him the most, he's useless!
Robin-senpai's in danger from all sides!
What do I do?! What do I do?!
Oh yeah!
Will you face me, Bartolomeo?
I can only put up one barrier at a time.
That's the drawback, but I don't care.
Robin-senpai! If I can save you, I won't hesitate!
Barrier Ball!
Go ahead, blow up if you like!
We're inside my unbreakable barrier!
This fool...
Rooster-kun! Don't tell me you...
You were prepared to take me down with you?!
You insolent little...
Fashion Pop!
Rooster-kun!
That serves you right, hedgehog!
Now the wall won't rupture!
I did it...
I protected Robin-senpai.
Too bad for you, fool.
You missed by just a few centimeters.
It wasn't my throat that you stabbed. It was my shoulder.
I-I missed his vital organs?!
Sure, he was inflated and I couldn't tell if it was his neck or shoulder but...
Dammit!
You have Devil Fruit powers too,
so you know the deal.
As long as I'm conscious...
The wall rupture won't stop!
Watch closely as your friends are blown asunder!
Damn, I'm such a fool!
Nico Robin, I'm sorry!
I brought Hakuba under control!
I'm Cavendish now!
But I left half of me as Hakuba.
Let go of me! I'll kill you!
I'll take you to the Sunflower Field with Hakuba's speed!
I'll use Hakuba's abilities!
We have no other options! Let go of me!
Trust me!
Which one's talking?
No time to think!
Hurry up!
D-Don't!
Pop Rock...
Super Arena!
Robin-senpai!
This barrier of yours is quite convenient.
Look.
There's nothing left of either one.
Huh?!
Why did you stop me?!
It's your own body!
If so, why don't you...
listen to me every now and then?!
Cien Fleur! Spider Net!
Hundred Flower Spider Net
You stopped Hakuba's sword for me, didn't you, Cabbage-kun?
You're such a confusing man.
Impossible!
How could they escape that rupture?!
Compared to him, I'm pathetic!
Divine Homage Fist!
Luffy-senpai...
My skills aren't good enough now...
But I'll become stronger and stronger...
Barrier...
I swear, that someday...
I'll become a man who can help you!
Pistol!
I barely won using my senpai's power...
Anyway, I never want to...
work with that annoying guy again!
4th Step
Sunflower Hill
It's quite noisy down there, too.
On an unstable battlefield like this,
even a gladiator from the Colosseum would totter and fall!
Right, Rebecca?
Vipera Glaive!
Snake Sword
Don't!
Run, Rebecca! You can't stop that attack!
Butterfly flowers that divert attacks...
Mil Fleur!
Thousand Flower
Moth Orchid!
Robin-san!
That's...
Robiland!
You've completed your objective, Rebecca.
Thank you for delivering the key.
From now on, I'll defend you!